H. Alexander Smith Papers, 1897-1966 (bulk 1920-1966 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- 32101076562626 (Box 591)
- 32101076562634 (Box 592)
- 32101076562642 (Box 593)
- 32101076562659 (Box 594)
- 32101076562667 (Box 595)
- 32101076562675 (Box 596)
- 32101076562683 (Box 597)
- 32101076562691 (Box 598)
- 32101076562709 (Box 599)
- 32101076562717 (Box 600)
- 32101076562725 (Box 601)
- 32101076562733 (Box 602)
- 32101076562741 (Box 603)
- 32101076562758 (Box 604)
- 32101076562766 (Box 605)
- 32101076562774 (Box 606)
- 32101076562782 (Box 607)
- 32101076562790 (Box 608)
- 32101076562808 (Box 609)
- 32101076562816 (Box 610)
- 32101076562824 (Box 611)
- 32101076562832 (Box 612)
- 32101076562840 (Box 613)
- 32101076562857 (Box 614)
- 32101076562865 (Box 615)
- 32101076562873 (Box 616)
- 32101076562881 (Box 617)
- 32101076562899 (Box 618)
- 32101076562907 (Box 619)
- 32101076562915 (Box 620)
- 32101076562923 (Box 621)
- 32101076562931 (Box 622)
- 32101076562949 (Box 623)
- 32101076562956 (Box 624)
- 32101076562964 (Box 625)
- 32101076562972 (Box 626)
- 32101076562980 (Box 627)
- 32101076562998 (Box 628)
- 32101076563004 (Box 629)
- 32101076563012 (Box 630)
- 32101076563020 (Box 631)
- 32101076563038 (Box 632)
- 32101076563046 (Box 633)
- 32101076563053 (Box 634)
- 32101076563061 (Box 635)
- 32101076563079 (Box 636)
- 32101076563087 (Box 637)
- 32101076563095 (Box 638)
- 32101076563103 (Box 639)
- 32101076563111 (Box 640)
- 32101076563129 (Box 641)
- 32101076563137 (Box 642)
- 32101076563145 (Box 643)
- 32101076563152 (Box 644)
- 32101076563160 (Box 645)
- 32101076563178 (Box 646)
- 32101076563186 (Box 647)
- 32101076563194 (Box 648)
- 32101076563202 (Box 649)
- 32101076563210 (Box 650)
- 32101076563228 (Box 651)
- 32101076563236 (Box 652)
- 32101076563244 (Box 653)
- 32101076563251 (Box 654)
- 32101076563269 (Box 655)
- 32101076563277 (Box 656)
- 32101076563285 (Box 657)
- 32101076563293 (Box 658)
- 32101076563301 (Box 659)
- 32101076563319 (Box 660)
- 32101076563327 (Box 661)
- 32101076563335 (Box 662)
- 32101076563343 (Box 663)
- 32101076563350 (Box 664)
- 32101076563368 (Box 665)